Hello everyone. My name is Maka Yamada from Nearly Called Joy.
Today, I'd like to do a visual shoot for the Millmode Pong stage.
Everyone will be transformed into cute characters for the visual shoot,
Please keep your eyes peeled for them.
I will be playing the role of Moon-kun.
Moon is a cute boy who is mysterious and quiet.
This is the first time I've played a character with a crisp, cool, straight face,
The staff told me how cute and cool he was,
I think I did my best in filming the scene.
This was my first stage performance as Nielly Cole Joy,
I'm going to do my best,
I often feel that my tongue is not good for me,
I have a smooth tongue and a loud voice to begin with, so I'm going to do my best to make use of it,
So I will do my best to use my voice and my smoothness.
My name is Mizuki Oshina.
The role I will be playing this time is Hanzo,
I'm playing the role of Hanzo, an ancient character of the one Lemon is playing,
He is a bit of a goofball,
He is a bit of a goofball, but he is also a lovable character that you can't help but hate.
I was really nervous,
I was really nervous, but I inputted Hanzo,
I think I made a goofy face.
I think I did a good job of making a goofy face with a fluffy mouth,
I think I scored 100 points.
This is my first time on stage in New Zealand,
I will do my best to make it a performance that will leave a lasting impression on as many people as possible.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Hello everyone. My name is Airiko Yamano and I am an actress with New News Call.
I played the role of Puppy.
I was so nervous and nervous,
I'm really happy to have such a cute costume and hair and makeup done for me.
Thank you very much.
I also had my picture taken and a video of Chaho-san taken.
I'm very nervous to perform on stage,
I will do my best to memorize the lines perfectly.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
I will be playing the role of a beautiful girl.
My name is Riko Fujisawa.
This beauty is a narcissist,
She is a very knowledgeable girl who studies or explores beauty,
She knows a lot about beauty,
So I would like to improve my knowledge of beauty and do my best.
This is my first time on stage as well,
I hope you will enjoy it,
I will do my best to create a wonderful world of Millemodepont with beautiful people and everyone.
I will do my best. Please do your best.
I just finished shooting the visuals for the stage.
My name is Riko Fujisawa, and I will be playing the role of Peta.
Peta has a very kind heart,
She can cry for others,
She is the kind of girl that I want to be,
I am very happy to be able to play the role of Peta,
I am very happy to be able to play this role.
I am a little worried about whether I will be able to memorize the script,
But I am sure that by the time this is published, I will have finished it without any problems,
We will practice a lot so that we can finish without any mistakes,
I will do my best to deliver a wonderful Peta.
Thank you for your hard work.
I will be playing the role of Yashichi,
I will be playing the role of Yashichi, but not in the costume of the music video or something,
What do you call it? role?
It's my first time to wear the costume and I'm not sure if it suits me well,
I'm not sure if I look good in the costume for the first time, but I really hope I can act the part as well as I can.
I will do my best.
I'll do my best to recreate the world of the anime repo.
I will do my best. I look forward to working with you.
My name is Aoi Onishi.
I will be playing the role of Gabeen.
The role of Gabeen is a little bit negative,
I'm going to try to make a troubled expression or something like that.Hello, I am Ayumi Ozawa of Miyagi Takahashi. I am Ayumi Ozawa of Miyagi Takahashi.
This time I will be playing the role of Sasaki, the Sasaki of MOMODEPON.
I was nervous, but I knew it would be a different kind of shooting for the stage,
It is a different atmosphere from the usual filming and shooting that I am allowed to do,
I was able to see a different side of myself from the Ayumi Ozawa who usually performs in Miyagi,
It was a lot of fun, and the members were very cute,
I'm really looking forward to seeing the finished product.
I am very much looking forward to the completion of the show,
I would like to thank everyone who has always supported me,
I would like to thank all of you who have always supported us, and also to the fans of the original work,
I will do my best to create and deliver the world view of "Momodepon" to all of you who have always supported us and to the fans of the original work.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
My role is Lilum-chan,
She is so cute, and she is so cute that I can't help but think of her as a little girl,
She is a little bit bad at magic,
She is a little bit bad at magic, so I think the scenes where she is using magic are very cute when she is exerting herself.
Her hair and costumes are also very cute,
It was really like we were fairies on set,
We had a lot of fun filming.
Thank you very much.
This is the first time for me to perform on stage with Mearly Cole Joy, so I am very nervous,
I am very nervous,
I am very nervous, but we are all working together and deepening our bond until the performance,
We have been working together to strengthen our bond,
I hope to be able to show that on stage,
I hope that I can show you how I feel on stage, and that I can really get into the role,
I would like to do my best from now on.
Hello everyone.
I will be playing the role of Mia in this production.
My name is Kana Amano, and I play the role of Mary Cole Joy.
I am wearing this costume,
I was very nervous.
I was very nervous,
But they were very kind to me,
I have been watching the show since I was a little girl, and I am very proud to be a part of it.
I have been watching them since I was a little girl,
I am very happy to have been able to watch the film since I was a child,
I am very happy to have been able to watch the film since I was a little girl,
I am very happy to be able to perform such a wonderful work
I am so grateful to be able to perform such a wonderful work at the Mairie Cole Joy,
I am very grateful to be able to perform such a wonderful work at Mary Cole Joy,
I can't thank you enough for allowing us to perform,
I will work hard on the stage with a sense of respect for this wonderful work,
I will do my very best to perform with respect for this wonderful work.
I look forward to working with you all.
Thank you very much.
I found it, Milmo-sama!
Lil' Mo hugging Milmo.
Wow, don't hug me, get away from me!
And Milmo, who shooed him away.
Why are you shy?
We're engaged to be married.
That's something your parents decided on their own.
Let's make a plan, then.
Oh, man!
Yamano.
The three of us will be gone.
Your brother's in danger.
Puppy shows up.
Murumo.
Hey, Papi, what are you doing here?
I don't have time for Puppy right now. I'm going that way.
Shoo-shoo, you're terrible!
I'm wasting my time.
What? Is that what you want me to do? I'm not playing with you anymore.
No, I'm popular and idolized, so I don't need Puppy's attention at all. I'm sure you're disappointed.
I'm sure he was disappointed that we happened to meet Murumo.
Thank you for watching.
So, it's time for the Haraon Pro!
We've got about 30 minutes left.
I'm nervous. I'm really nervous.
It's been about a month now.
I've been working really hard.
I've been trying to get them to build it up.
They're going to enjoy it like it's never going to end.
I'll be waiting for the Odaiba to be shipped from now on too!
Thank you very much for your hard work.
I don't know what to do
I'll just hold on to my paper
I'll just pinch myself
If something goes wrong, it's softI am filled with gratitude once again for the opportunity to be a part of this event and I look forward to working hard in the future.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much for coming to Stage Mill Modecon.
Please wait for a while until the show starts.
Today's presenters were Amano Onoato as Milmo and Yuka Murayama as Dirumu.
See you later!
Please take your seats.
For the convenience of the performance, we will be guiding you to the evacuation exits in the auditorium.
We will be aware of this.
Please check the nearest emergency exit by yourself beforehand.
Please check the nearest emergency exit by yourself.
In case of emergency, please wait at your seat,
Please wait at your seat.
U-Tuner
I am a friend of Millmo
Friends of Millmo Friends
Friends of Friends
Friends of Millmo's Friends
Who's that?
No more! It will be a little while before Milmo and Minami Frog meet.
Today, we're going to tell you the story of Milmo's graduation from kindergarten!
Hey, teacher, don't ignore me. Who the heck is Minami-mikaeru?
Still, it looks like the story is about to begin.
Oh, Milmo, Neelmo is coming from over there!
What a pain in the ass!
Milmo-sama! Milmo-sama!
What's wrong? It's strange, isn't it?
I'm sure I saw Milmo-sama around here.
Did I see him wrong? I went to the trouble of getting some delicious chocolates.
Chocolate? I found it!
Milmo-sama!
Let's get away from him!
Why are you shy?
Aren't we committed to each other?
That's what our parents decided on their own.
Is there a graduation exam for the training school?
Now's the time to get soft and fluffy with Milmo.
Hey! Help! Hanzo!
Yassun!
It's Myung-sama.
Yes, actually.
Here's a little something for you, bro.
Here's a cleaner I picked up.
Shut up!
It's a cleaner!
I've got a good degree to throw in there!
That's right, you can't throw a cleaner with a good degree. Cleaner... you can't throw a good degree.
I'm sorry, bro.
I'm only trained to make people happy through magic.
If we couldn't save Milmo here, we'd still be graduating.
With our help, we'll all live another year.
We'll graduate together.
That's for sure.
I'm going out of my mind when Milmo bows down to me.
I'm sure Anna will agree with me.
I'm sad that I won't be graduating.
But I'm even sadder that Lil' Lum will change.
Hey, guys.
Thank you.
I don't think there's such a thing as magical magic.
I don't think there's such a thing as magical magic
There's magic in it, but I want my precious feelings back
It takes magic, but it's the power of the mind
I like to listen to sound.
Mi-Ma?
Mi-Ma!
What's that? That's unusual, isn't it?
It's not like her to be so quiet.
Well, she's happy, that's all that matters.
Let go of me!
What?
Not from me!
She's embarrassed, Myrma.
I'm not embarrassed! I can't get it off!
It won't come off!
I wish I could go back to this feeling!
To all the people involved in creating this stage, and to the fans who always support us,
and all the fans who always support us,
and the members of Sambra,
Sambra, I am filled with gratitude to all of you.
I am so happy to have been able to work in such a wonderful environment,
I am so happy to have been able to work in such a wonderful environment and to create this stage.
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you all.
I am Equal Doc.
I look forward to working with you.
Everyone.We can't do anything yet,
We hope to be able to bring happiness and smiles to everyone by ourselves someday.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
I'm so happy.
You all look happy.
I was feeling really sentimental until just now,
I didn't want to leave you all, but now I'm so happy.
I got it, so wait a minute.
I can't name her.
We are going to hold our first concert on May 3.
Thank you very much.
Once again, thank you very much for your time today.
This concludes the Miyamic All Jai Spare Live Stage Mew Robo de Bong! All performances have come to an end.
Thank you very much for your support, coming and watching.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
We have been supported by so many people since our rehearsals, and we have been touched by the kindness of so many people,
We, all the members, are very happy to have been given such a big stage job by Nearly Coal John.
I am filled with gratitude.
We all felt miserable because it was the first time for us to perform on stage,
I think it is important to understand how it feels to be on stage in a production of "Dream Model Pong," which is loved by so many people,
I also wondered what kind of feelings we should have when we were adapting a work that is loved by so many people to the stage,
I was also thinking about how to express the good qualities of the women and the work on the stage,
We have been practicing and going through a lot of things every day,
I am very happy that all of the members are now able to celebrate the Raku with success.
We have been able to come this far because of all the people who have made this event possible,
I am truly grateful to all the people who have made this possible, to all the people involved, and to all the fans who have been a part of this event,
We are truly grateful to all of you.
We are still in our infancy with this first concert, but we are very happy to have had this great opportunity,
We are still in our infancy, but we have been given such a great and wonderful opportunity,
I hope to use this opportunity to grow even more,
I hope we can use this opportunity to grow even more, and to bring you more energy and happiness,
I would like to devote myself more and more to this opportunity.
Thank you very much.
undefined